<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Olga Frolova – Technical Project Manager | Driving Innovation in Tech &amp; AI on Olga Frolova</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Olga Frolova – Technical Project Manager | Driving Innovation in Tech &amp; AI on Olga Frolova</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:43:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I Switched to Kagi (And What Happened Next)</title>
      <link>/posts/kagi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/kagi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I switched to Kagi in March 2025 - I’d been disappointed for a while and wanted a fresh approach to searching online. I decided it was time for a change after three major frustrations with Google: the flood of low-quality and spammy websites cluttering my search results, the constant interruption from targeted advertisements during research, and serious concerns about how my personal data was being collected and used. I wanted a search engine that could deliver trustworthy information without tracking my every move or prioritizing advertisers over actual answers.
So, I decided to try Kagi, a subscription-based search engine. What sealed the deal was learning about their privacy protections: Kagi proxies all images to prevent tracking from third parties and uses HTTPS encryption across their platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:08:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; align-items: center; gap: 20px; margin-bottom: 20px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;h1&gt;Olga Frolova&lt;/h1&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a Technical Project Manager with experience in managing software and web projects, including GenAI-powered prototypes. Based in Montreal, QC, I specialize in leading cross-functional teams and delivering projects on time and within budget.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/images/Olga_Frolova_MBA_photo.png&#34; alt=&#34;Olga Frolova&#34; style=&#34;width: 250px; height: auto; border-radius: 5px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;bkom-studios-montreal-qc-remote&#34;&gt;BKOM Studios, Montreal, QC (Remote)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Manager &amp;amp; Producer&lt;/strong&gt; | February 2021 - Present&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managed small and large-scale mobile software and web projects, including GenAI-powered prototypes for Hasbro, partnerships with Lego, AMC Network&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Walking Dead&amp;rdquo; universe, and Paizo Inc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led and executed a company-wide AI training program, enhancing team capabilities in cutting-edge technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directed teams in navigating complex implementation challenges while meeting deadlines and fulfilling business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversaw creative and development teams, fostering collaboration and communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;advisor-websites-vancouver-bc&#34;&gt;Advisor Websites, Vancouver, BC&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Team Manager&lt;/strong&gt; | March 2017 - February 2021&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work with Me</title>
      <link>/work_with_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 10:08:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/work_with_me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am available for consulting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizations I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with include: Hasbro, Mattel, Lego, AMC Network, Paizo Inc, SunLife, Desjardins, and LPL Financial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;services-i-offer&#34;&gt;Services I Offer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GenAI-powered prototype development and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI strategy and workflow optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-functional team leadership and coordination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product roadmap development and execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical project planning and delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stakeholder management and client communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resource allocation and budget management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile methodology implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise account management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;testimonials&#34;&gt;Testimonials&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I had the pleasure of working with Olga for many years at BKOM Studios, where she consistently demonstrated her exceptional skills as a producer and project manager. She played a key role in the successful delivery of numerous games and apps, collaborating seamlessly with engineering, design, art, and other teams. Her ability to keep projects on track while maintaining high-quality standards made her an invaluable asset to the team.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Adoption Gap</title>
      <link>/posts/the_ai_adoption_gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 09:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/the_ai_adoption_gap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-ai-adoption-gap&#34;&gt;The AI Adoption Gap&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early on in my career as a producer in the game industry, I was already experimenting with AI tools, long before &amp;ldquo;generative AI&amp;rdquo; became the talk of the town. I had a hunch that LLMs held enormous potential not just for programming but for every aspect of game development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;from-debugging-to-art-the-ai-adoption-gap&#34;&gt;From Debugging to Art: The AI Adoption Gap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the technical side of my projects, we embraced AI pretty readily: LLM-based assistance helped squash bugs, write unit tests, and provide code reviews. Tools like GitHub Copilot and Cursor.com integrated seamlessly into our pipelines; my dev team loved the productivity boost and was far from intimidated. However, the story was different in the art and design departments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
