<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Olga Frolova</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Olga Frolova</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 09:43:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Use Cursor as a Technical Project Manager: A Step-by-Step</title>
      <link>/posts/how-i-use-cursor-as-a-technical-project-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 09:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-i-use-cursor-as-a-technical-project-manager/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How I Use Cursor as a Technical Project Manager: A Step-by-Step
AI-Driven Workflow For the past two years, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed projects with an
AI-first, system-led mindset. I train my team to work the same way. At
our company, we use Cursor. It&amp;rsquo;s the same tool our engineers and
technical specialists use daily, which already makes it a natural fit
for managing technical work. But it goes further. Cursor runs fast as a
desktop app, supports markdown with live previews, integrates directly
with Jira, Confluence, and Notion through MCPs, and gives me access to
multiple LLMs in one place. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to jump between tools or
reformat the same content twice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Switched to Kagi (And What Happened Next)</title>
      <link>/posts/kagi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/kagi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I switched to Kagi in March 2025 - I’d been disappointed for a while and wanted a fresh approach to searching online. I decided it was time for a change after three major frustrations with Google: the flood of low-quality and spammy websites cluttering my search results, the constant interruption from targeted advertisements during research, and serious concerns about how my personal data was being collected and used. I wanted a search engine that could deliver trustworthy information without tracking my every move or prioritizing advertisers over actual answers.
So, I decided to try Kagi, a subscription-based search engine. What sealed the deal was learning about their privacy protections: Kagi proxies all images to prevent tracking from third parties and uses HTTPS encryption across their platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen AI Highlights of 2024: A Year in Review</title>
      <link>/posts/gen_ai_highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/gen_ai_highlights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As 2024 wraps up, I wanted to share a quick rundown of the major generative AI developments that stood out this year. This post is based on a presentation I gave back in December, drawing from research and hands-on experience applying these tools to projects (especially at the prototype stage) in the video game industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gpt-4o-smarter-clearer-more-capable&#34;&gt;GPT-4o: Smarter, Clearer, More Capable&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest leap came from &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com&#34;&gt;OpenAI&lt;/a&gt; with the release of GPT-4o. What makes this model stand out isn’t just its speed but how well it reasons. It walks you through its logic step by step, which makes it especially useful for complex math, debugging code, or explaining difficult concepts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Adoption Gap</title>
      <link>/posts/the_ai_adoption_gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 09:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/the_ai_adoption_gap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-ai-adoption-gap&#34;&gt;The AI Adoption Gap&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early on in my career as a producer in the game industry, I was already experimenting with AI tools, long before &amp;ldquo;generative AI&amp;rdquo; became the talk of the town. I had a hunch that LLMs held enormous potential not just for programming but for every aspect of game development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;from-debugging-to-art-the-ai-adoption-gap&#34;&gt;From Debugging to Art: The AI Adoption Gap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the technical side of my projects, we embraced AI pretty readily: LLM-based assistance helped squash bugs, write unit tests, and provide code reviews. Tools like GitHub Copilot and Cursor.com integrated seamlessly into our pipelines; my dev team loved the productivity boost and was far from intimidated. However, the story was different in the art and design departments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
